Set The Fire To Rain
压制:随Feng
歌手:Adele 阿黛尔
I let it fall, my heart
我把心 抛下
And as it fell, you rose to claim it
坠落之际 你挺身认领
It was dark and I was over
漆黑一片 我命休矣
Until you kissed my lips and you saved me
这时你吻我唇 救我一命
My hands, they were strong, but my knees were far too weak
我这双手 苍劲有力 可双膝却弱不禁风
To stand in your arms without falling to your feet
站在你怀里 才不会瘫倒于地
But there's a side to you that I never knew, never knew
可你藏有一面 不曾为我知 为我知
All the things you'd say, they were never true, never true
你所有的言语 不曾发于心 发于心
And the games you'd play, you would always win, always win
你所有的游戏 赢家总是你 总是你
But I set fire to the rain
而我烧起了一场雨
Watched it pour as I touched your face
轻抚你脸庞 细看雨滂沱
Well, it burned while I cried
雨在烧 我落泪
'Cause I heard it screaming out your name, your name
因为我听到它在拼命喊着你 喊着你
When laying with you I could stay there
与你共枕 我方可暂留那儿
Close my eyes, feel you here forever
合上双眼 感受你永留这儿
You and me together, nothing is better
你与我手相携 胜过世间一切
'Cause there's a side to you that I never knew, never knew
可你藏有一面 不曾为我知 为我知
All the things you'd say, they were never true, never true
你所有的言语 不曾发于心 发于心
And the games you'd play, you would always win, always win
你所有的游戏 赢家总是你 总是你
But I set fire to the rain
而我烧起了一场雨
Watched it pour as I touched your face
轻抚你脸庞 细看雨滂沱
Well, it burned while I cried
雨在烧 我落泪
'Cause I heard it screaming out your name, your name
因为我听到它在拼命喊着你 喊着你
I set fire to the rain
我烧起了一场雨
And I threw us into the flames
再把你我丢进火海
While it fell, something died
雨正酣 了一念
'Cause I knew that that was the last time, the last time
因为我知道了却的是前缘 是前缘
Sometimes I wake up by the door
有时我于门口醒来
That heart you caught must be waiting for you
你曾捕获的心定是在等你
Even now when we're already over
尽管如今 你我再无瓜葛
I can't help myself from looking for you
我仍禁不住要把你找寻
I set fire to the rain
我烧起了一场雨
Watched it pour as I touched your face
轻抚你脸庞 细看雨滂沱
Well, it burned while I cried
雨在烧 我落泪
'Cause I heard it screaming out your name, your name
因为我听到它在拼命喊着你 喊着你
I set fire to the rain
我烧起了一场雨
And I threw us into the flames
再把你我丢进火海
While it fell, something died
雨正酣 了一念
'Cause I knew that that was the last time, the last time, oh
因为我知道了却的是前缘 是前缘 噢
Oh, no
噢 不
Let it burn, oh
让雨烧 噢
Let it burn
让雨烧
压制:随Feng